Manaday Mavani

JavaScript Developer - MEAN Stack

A versatile and committed developer with **6+ years** of experience in popular **JavaScript** technologies. Part of **4 successful products** since inception, delivered **1 bespoke project** (phase 1) single handedly **at Investis**. Consulting as a **JavaScript freelancer** for **3 large projects**.

EXPERIENCE

Investis — Tech Lead

JUL 2010 - PRESENT, Vadodara

My roles and responsibilities have evolved over the time. My current responsibilities includes

- **Develop Dynamic Web Apps** using AngularJS and REST APIs.
- **Code review** and support junior team members.
- Prepare training materials and train freshers. Update freshers' progress to HR and Line Managers.
- Manage client communications and queries technical only.
- Conduct knowledge sharing sessions being a part of Technical Innovation Cell
- **Improve and automate** development tasks/processes

Freelancing

MAY 2016 - PRESENT

Can produce all details and work in person

Nomadic Solutions — Trainee .NET Developer

JAN 2010 - JUL 2010, Jamnagar

- Develop online recharge portal using .NET Technologies
- Develop and manage Tables, Stored Procedures in SQL Server

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Applications

MAR 2010 - Saurashtra University

Atmiya Institute of Technology and Science, Rajkot.

Bachelor of Commerce

MAY 2007 - Saurashtra University

P.D. Malaviya College of Commerce, Rajkot.

Vadodara, India. manaday.mavani (skype) m.k.mavani@gmail.com

SKILLS

JavaScript **** AngularJS (1.x) $\star \star \star \star \star$ NodeJS **** MongoDB **** **** ExpressJS REST API Dev & Design **** Gulp **** Git / SVN ****

Titanium Appcelerator, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PureCSS, jQuery, Lodash, Velocity JS, JWT, NPM, and Bower

AWARDS

Remarkable and Fantastic Colleague Investis, 2012

INTERESTS

<u>Photography</u>, <u>Blogging</u>, Table-Tennis

LANGUAGES

Gujarati, English, Hindi

PROJECTS

Investor Relations App (V1, V2, V3)

JAN 2010 - JUN 2015, **Investis**

Investor Relations app is a cross platform **Investis product** for iOS and Android devices. It has been sold to roughly 200 multinational clients like <u>adidas</u>, <u>ArcelorMittal</u>, and <u>Rolls Royce</u>.

Tools & Technologies: Titanium Appcelerator, Alloy, TiShadow, JavaScript, XML, Highcharts, SQLite

JetStream for Jet.com

JUN 2015 - NOV 2015, Investis

JetStream is an **enterprise iOS app** developed for Jet.com's employees and investors **to provide key business insights**. My responsibilities were to manage client comms and requirements, liaise with design head, and develop & deliver the phase-1.

More: http://www.businessinsider.com/jets-ceo-explains-why-the-company-shares-so-much-2016-3

Tools & Technologies: Titanium Appcelerator, Parse API, Alloy, JavaScript, SQLite

MyInvestis

JAN 2016 - PRESENT, Investis

MyInvestis is a **self-serve platform** for Investis clients. The current project is a complete **re-architecture** to enhance the overall UX and UI. My responsibilities include AngularJS development, support and code review juniors, and manage front-end build automation.

Tools & Technologies: HTML, CSS, AngularJS, Web API, PostgreSQL, Gulp

CERTIFICATIONS

- <u>Titanium Certified App Developer</u>, Jul 2012.
- M101JS: MongoDB for Node.js Developers, Mongo University, Mar 2016.
- AngularJS Masterclass, Udemy.com, Apr 2016.
- Project101x: Introduction to Project Management by The University of Adelaide on edx.com, Apr 2016.

COURSES

- Responsive Web Design Fundamentals by Google on Udacity.com
- Web Tooling and Automation by Google on Udacity.com
- Website Performance Optimization by Google on Udacity.com